David Stick Papers PC.5001
State Archives of North Carolina
- Photographs, 1909-2008 and undated; 45077; Stick, David, 1919-2009
  - Other Photographs, 1935-1999 and undated; 6743; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    - Wright Brothers [3 Folders], 1940s-1960s and undated; 29647; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Wright Brothers [3 Folders])
    - Wright Memorial Construction (circa 1931), 1992; 29648; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Wright Memorial Construction (1920s))